So next, getting on a step ladder, we're going to stand up here and start putting on our hillsides using a brush.
Nice brush.
I generally recommend being 2 to 3 inches wide.
And what we're going to do is you notice that the line here is really blocky.
Horizon lines don't look like this.
That's okay though.
Because what we're going to do.
Get lots of paint on your brush here and we're going to start coloring in the hills.
See like this nice rise and fall I'm getting?
And we're going to keep extending this throughout with gentle rises and falls.
Now this is going to be more detail put on.
You can see here where it's, get the line really fine.
But that also means the paint could be a little thin.
So be prepared for this even if you didn't have to with the rest of the base layer here.
Be prepared to have to put on multiple coats.
Which again, allowing about a day to maybe even two days to dry between coats.